Fraser Burrows

123 Main Street, San Francisco, CA 12345 f.burrows@email.conn [1231-45 6-7 891

Dedicated truck driver with 10+ years of experience making professional, punctual deliveries. Able to efficiently manage schedules and work to challenging deadlines. Clear communicator with strong teamwork skills and a thorough knowledge of navigation and DOT regulations.

Key Skills

- Professional and friendly customer service
- ♦ Clear communication skills
- Problem-solving
- Adept at using maps and navigation systems to plan the most efficient route
- Able to work independently and in teams of all sizes
- Excellent time-management

Professional Experience

Truck Driver

XPO Logistics Inc, Orange, CA { July 2015-Present

- Follow company procedures and local traffic laws to make safe, on-time deliveries
- Maintain up-to-date travel logs and delivery tracking records
- Communicate incidents and road traffic conditions that may affect deliveries to head office and other drivers using two-way radios
- Present a professional image reflecting the brand values

Truck Driver

Marten Transport, Los Angeles, CA j April 2012- July 2015

- Carried out punctual deliveries across the Los Angeles metropolitan area
- Safely loaded heavy cargo using mechanical lifts and secured them inside the truck to ensure they arrived in perfect condition
- Kept detailed load records and checked them regularly for accuracy

Truck Driver

YRC Freight, Sun Valley, CA (March 2008- April 2012

- Performed vehicle maintenance, cleaning, and safety checks before departure
- Navigated routes using maps, written directions, and satellite navigation systems
- Worked effectively as part of a team to complete deliveries efficiently and professionally

Education

High School Diploma

Lowell High School, San Francisco, CA, July 2008

Certifications

◆ Class A CDL License, 2008